question_data_orignal = [
{"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "T" , "choice" : ["red", "yellow"] },
{"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "Fe" , "choice" : ["fat", "ele"] },
{"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "T" , "choice" : ["500", "400"] },
{"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "T" , "choice" : ["1ball", "2ball"] },
{"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "T" , "choice" : ["carr", "marr"] },
{"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "F" , "choice" : ["state", "fun"] },
{"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "T" , "choice" : ["ocds", "por"] },
{"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "F" , "choice" : ["staT", "down"] },
{"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "T" , "choice" : ["back", "rub"] },
{"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "T" , "choice" : ["name", "moon"] },
{"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "F" , "choice" : ["half", "more"] },
{"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "T" , "choice" : ["sma", "rip"] }
]

[{'title': 'Quizas'}, {'stem': '1. What is the capital of France?', 'options': [' London', ' Paris', ' Madrid', ' Rome'], 'answer': 'B'}, {'stem': '2. Which planet is known as the Red Planet?', 'options': [' Jupiter', ' Mars', ' Saturn', ' Venus'], 'answer': 'B'}, {'stem': '3. Who painted the Mona Lisa?', 'options': [' Vincent van Gogh', ' Leonardo da Vinci', ' Pablo Picasso', ' Michelangelo'], 'answer': 'B'}, {'stem': '4. What is the tallest mountain in the world?', 'options': [' Mount Kilimanjaro', ' Mount Everest', ' Mount McKinley', ' Mount Fuji'], 'answer': 'B'}, {'stem': '5. Which country is known as the "Land of the Rising Sun"?5. Which country is known as the "Land of the Rising Sun"?', 'options': [' China', ' Japan', ' India', ' Australia'], 'answer': 'B'}, {'stem': '6. What is the largest ocean on Earth?6. What is the largest ocean on Earth?', 'options': [' Atlantic Ocean', ' Indian Ocean', ' Arctic Ocean', ' Pacific Ocean'], 'answer': 'D'}, {'stem': '7. Who wrote the play "Romeo and Juliet"?7. Who wrote the play "Romeo and Juliet"?', 'options': [' William Shakespeare', ' Ernest Hemingway', ' F. Scott Fitzgerald', ' Jane Austen'], 'answer': 'A'}, {'stem': '8. What is the chemical symbol for gold?8. What is the chemical symbol for gold?', 'options': [' Go', ' Au', ' Ag', ' Ge'], 'answer': 'B'}, {'stem': '9. In which year did World War II end?9. In which year did World War II end?', 'options': [' 1943', ' 1945', ' 1950', ' 1918'], 'answer': 'B'}, {'stem': '10. Which animal is known as the "King of the Jungle"?', 'options': ['Tiger', 'Lion', 'Elephant', 'Giraffe'], 'answer': 'B'}]

#what was imported
question_data = [
    {
        'stem': '1. What is the capital of France?',
        'options': [' London', ' Paris', ' Madrid', ' Rome'],
        'answer': 'B'
    },
    {
        'stem': '2. Which planet is known as the Red Planet?',
        'options': [' Jupiter', ' Mars', ' Saturn', ' Venus'],
        'answer': 'B'
    },
    {
        'stem': '3. Who painted the Mona Lisa?',
        'options': [' Vincent van Gogh', ' Leonardo da Vinci', ' Pablo Picasso', ' Michelangelo'],
        'answer': 'B'
    },
    {
        'stem': '4. What is the tallest mountain in the world?',
        'options': [' Mount Kilimanjaro', ' Mount Everest', ' Mount McKinley', ' Mount Fuji'],
        'answer': 'B'
    },
    {
        'stem': '5. Which country is known as the "Land of the Rising Sun"?',
        'options': [' China', ' Japan', ' India', ' Australia'],
        'answer': 'B'
    },
       {
        'stem': '6. What is the largest ocean on Earth?',
        'options': [' Atlantic Ocean', ' Indian Ocean', ' Arctic Ocean', ' Pacific Ocean'],
        'answer': 'D'
    },
    {
        'stem': '7. Who wrote the play "Romeo and Juliet"?',
        'options': [' William Shakespeare', ' Ernest Hemingway', ' F. Scott Fitzgerald', ' Jane Austen'],
        'answer': 'A'
    },
    {
        'stem': '8. What is the chemical symbol for gold?',
        'options': [' Go', ' Au', ' Ag', ' Ge'],
        'answer': 'B'
    },
    {
        'stem': '9. In which year did World War II end?',
        'options': [' 1943', ' 1945', ' 1950', ' 1918'],
        'answer': 'B'
    },
    {
        'stem': '10. Which animal is known as the "King of the Jungle"?',
        'options': ['Tiger', 'Lion', 'Elephant', 'Giraffe'],
        'answer': 'B'
    }

]

 